let questions = [
    {
        numb: 1,
        question: "What is CSS used for?",
        answer: "D. For Styling",
        options: [
            "A. For Modification",
             " B. For playing",
            "C. For flyer",
            "D. For Styling"    

        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 2,
        question: "What does HTML do?",
        answer: "A. Structure a website",
        options: [
            "A. Structure a website",
            "B. Build the full website",
            "C. Making website Interactive",
            "D. For Styling"

        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 3,
        question: "What does SQL stand for?",
        answer: "D. Structure Query Language",
        options: [
            "A. Strength Query Language",
            "B. Stylesheet Query Language",
            "C. Science Question Language",
            "D. Structure Query Language"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 4,
        question: "What does UL stand for?",
        answer: "A. Unorderd List",
        options: [
             "A. Unorderd List",
            "B. Under List",
            "C. United Level",
            "D. Understant List"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 5,
        question: "What does OL stand for?",
        answer: "B. Orderd List",
        options: [
            "A. Over List",
            "B. Orderd List",
            "C. Operate Level",
            "D. Ordinary List"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 6,
        question: "What is color used for in CSS?",
        answer: "A. Change text color",
        options: [
            "A. Change text color",
            "B. Chand background color",
            "C. Color the website",
            "D. Make color work"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 7,
        question: "what is does <img> tag represent in HTML?",
        answer: "C. To input an image in a website",
        options: [
             "A. To change the images in a website",
            "B. To generate image",
            "C. To input an image in a website",
            "D. To suggest an image"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 8,
        question: "what is the <a> tag used for?",
        answer: "A. To input a link in a website",
        options: [
             "A. To input a link in a website",
            "B. To generate a link",
            "C. To improve a link",
            "D. To suggest a link"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 9,
        question: "What does the <p> tag represent?",
        answer: "C. Paragraph",
        options: [
             "A. People",
            "B Purple",
            "C. Paragraph",
            "D. Paper"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 10,
        question: "<h1> means?",
        answer: "A. Header one",
        options: [
             "A. Header one",
            "B Help one",
            "C. Holder one",
            "D. Help Online"
        ]
    } 
]